Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
(AIR HISSING)
(WOMAN PANTING)
(WHIMPERING)
(SCREECHING)
(SCREAMING)
(WHIRRING)
(GROANING)
(MAN PANTING)
Oh. my God. Oh. my God.
MAN: She's still breathing.
Call 911. Hurry up. Call 911.
Kiss me.
Hello. Yeah. I was
in a car accident
and a woman got hit.
She's hurt really bad.
She's just lying on the ground.
She's still breathing.
(INDISTINCT TALKING
ON POLICE RADIO)
Driver of the car is Leroy Kent.
Says he's driving
home from work.
drives onto the bridge.
sees the victim running.
she runs right
in front of his car.
Says it happened so
fast. couldn't do anything.
Get an ID on the vic?
No wallet. no purse. Looks
like she just got out of bed.
Did Mr. Kent have
anything to drink?
He's had a couple.
but he's under the limit.
Any witnesses? Well.
driver said there
was one other guy.
Told him to call 911.
but he didn't stick around.
We got guys out
doing a canvass now.
Mr. Kent. Yes.
How are you feeling?
Is she dead?
Yeah.
At first I thought
she might be okay.
I mean. the guy said
she was still breathing.
Is this the guy who
told you to call 911?
Yes. I ran over there
as soon as it happened
and he just walked up.
Where'd he go?
I don't know. I called 911. I
looked back. he was gone.
Any idea what he looked like?
Not really. no.
I was pretty shook up. I
was paying attention to her.
We're done. if you
guys want to take a look.
Yeah.
Thank you. Mr. Kent.
Barefoot. ready for bed.
but still wearing makeup.
Maybe she wasn't alone.
We've got some glass here.
Windshield didn't shatter
and headlights are still intact.
This didn't come
from the accident.
There's no cuts or
abrasions on her feet.
The guy said she was running.
She couldn't have run too far.
I wonder where
she was running to.
Or what she was running from.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
(IN FRENCH)
I'll call when it's finished.
HARPER: Notice
the iris is fully dilated.
filling the eye completely.
Looks like a shark's
eye. Is that normal?
Well. there's usually
dilation after death.
but I've never seen
anything like this before.
You get a tox report?
Preliminary says she
had a few drinks. not a lot.
Alcohol was .06.
What about drugs?
So far none of
the usual suspects.
Finding the unusual is
going to take a little more time.
Any sign of sexual assault?
No. But there was
something interesting.
No crush on the lungs.
What does that mean?
She was asphyxiated. but it
wasn't a result of the accident.
Someone suffocated her
after she was hit by the car?
So we got a homicide?
These contusions around
her nose and mouth.
looks like somebody
pinched off her air.
HANK: I got a hit on her prints.
The victim's name
was Faith Collins. 33.
Busted for a DUI a few months
ago. License was suspended.
Get an address?
About a mile away
from where she got hit.
We knew she didn't run very far.
so it makes sense
that she lived close by.
Well. maybe she was
running from home.
I think maybe she was running
from her husband. Roy Collins.
Got a record for spousal abuse.
(WHIRRING)
You Roy Collins?
What'd she tell you?
She saying I hit her?
She didn't say anything.
Well. that's different.
She usually complains
about everything I do.
Well. she's not going to
be complaining anymore.
We found your
wife's body last night.
What? Your wife's been murdered.
Oh. no.
I know this is difficult. but we need
to know the last time you saw her.
(STUTTERING) Last night.
What happened?
I came home. and I was hungry.
Faith wouldn't get off
the computer. like always.
She's got to connect
with her 322 friends.
I mean. who the
hell's got 322 friends?
I mean. I'm hungry.
I've been working all day.
So you argued? Yeah.
And she walked
out. you know. mad.
I didn't mean anything I said.
Well. did she tell you
where she was going?
No. You go after her?
No. NICK: About what
time did she leave?
I don't know. 10:00
or something like that.
So she left. you stayed
home. That's your story?
It's the truth.
Anybody see you?
You talk to anybody?
No.
I was waiting for
her to come back.
She always comes back.
You guys think I did
something to her?
You think I'd kill
my wife? Did you?
Want to do yourself a favor?
Why don't you come
downtown with us.
we'll put you in a
lineup. What do you say?
You want me for a
lineup? Arrest me.
But you don't got anything
on me. 'cause I didn't do it.
Where is she?
Her body's in the morgue.
When do I get her?
Somebody will contact you.
RENARD: What do you got?
NICK: Well. according
to her credit card.
Faith had a couple drinks at a bar
called the Blue Moon at around 10:30.
Bartender said she
talked up a couple locals.
but she left alone.
She didn't have her car.
Her license is suspended.
We're checking with cab companies
now to see who picked her up.
Called to the house four
times for domestic disturbance.
The husband's been
arrested twice for abuse.
I mean. it sounds like a battered
wife who couldn't break the cycle.
You sure the
husband's not covering?
Could be. He admits
to arguing with her.
Any chance she talked
to a family member
about her problems last night?
No calls on her cell after 9:00.
What about her 322 friends. Maybe
she reached out to one of them.
Hey. check it. She
posted last night.
Looks like a park.
Or a private garden.
What time did she send it?
11:37. Now if this was
taken from her cell phone.
the GPS coordinates should
be embedded in the file. right?
1516 Longacre Road.
Map it.
That's right here.
HANK: Right near the bridge.
NICK: Definitely
running distance.
Click "location."
"The Bramble Haus.
Bed and Breakfast."
You know it?
When do I have time
for a bed or breakfast?
Let's check with
the cab companies.
see if they made any drop-offs
at a B&B you don't have time for.
Not bad. You should make
time for a place like this.
Check out this '67 MGB Roadster.
You ready for a
little bit of trivia?
Royal blue and chrome bumpers.
Collectors call that
model right there
"the most desirable
MG ever made."
Impressed? Mildly.
BILLY: Of course.
Yes. I remember her.
She came in. I'd
say. it was after 11:00.
I was in the kitchen pulling
up some biscuits for breakfast
and I heard the bell ring.
so I went and got the door.
Oh! Excuse me a minute.
I've got your bill right here.
I hope everything
was to your liking.
Oh. Billy. we just love
this place. It's so magical.
Thank you. Thank you.
MAN: Yeah. we'll see
you on our anniversary.
BILLY: I look forward
to it. And tell your friends.
WOMAN: Five stars on Yelp.
And. you two. you guys
are going to love this place.
Newlyweds. They're
a third of my business.
So. I'm sorry. where were we?
The girl.
Of course. right. yes. Um...
I showed her a
room and the garden.
But she didn't stay?
No. she didn't
have a bag with her.
I'm sorry is there a problem?
A cab dropped her off
and didn't pick her up.
Can you explain that?
I really don't know.
I mean. if they don't want
to stay. I can't force them to.
You know. to tell you the truth.
she seemed a little bit
concerned or troubled.
And it's not really my
place to get involved
in guests' personal lives. so...
Can we see the garden?
Of course. yes. Oh...
But I warn you. you
might want to stay.
(LAUGHS)
Oh! Excuse me.
No problem.
Hey.
Yeah. this is the place. She
came here and then what?
I showed her these amber
roses that bloom only in Portland.
and my flowering wisteria.
And of course. the agapanthus.
but don't get me
started on those.
And then she said she
wanted to sit for a moment
and gather her thoughts.
so I said that this...
Be careful where you
step! That's... (SQUISHING)
Sorry. I didn't mean to do that.
The toad is an
endangered species.
It's the first sign of our
extinction when toads die.
I'm sorry. I didn't see it.
Well. if you can
think of anything else.
Of course. Yes. I'll
contact you immediately.
Would you like me
to show you out?
No. We're good.
Hey.
Have a good day.
That's all I got. Jim.
Let me know if you
need anything else. yeah?
Can I help you?
Yes. I'm looking into the
death of a friend of mine.
He was shot by one
of your detectives.
Are you a lawyer? No.
Just a friend of the family.
Here's the newspaper
article. I brought it along
so you'd know what
I was talking about.
Take a seat. please.
WU: He wants to talk to
the officer who shot his friend.
What did you tell him?
I told him we don't give out
that information. Sir. he's waiting.
How do you want
me to handle this?
Tell him the
detective's not available.
that someone from the
department will get back to him.
Yes. sir.
Make sure to get his
name. number and address.
Do a background check
and get back to me.
(INAUDIBLE)
The cab picked her up from the bar.
but why did she go to the Bramble Haus?
She was probably just
looking for a place to stay
so she wouldn't
have to go back home.
Cab driver could
have recommended it.
What does it matter.
she didn't stay.
That's what we need to find out.
She went there.
but she didn't stay.
And she didn't
call for another cab.
So you're thinking she
ran from there to the bridge.
I think we have to run a
background check on Billy Capra.
See if any other women
have had trouble at his place.
Also. run a check on unsolved
attacks on women or missing women.
NICK: "June. 1895.
"Kitzbuhel Alps.
south of Rattenberg.
"I have followed and observed
"a goat-like creature
for several days now.
"I have finally been able to
identify him as a Ziegevolk.
"Sometimes known as Bluebeards.
"I now know he is responsible
for defiling several women
"who seemed to fallen
under some sort of spell.
"I have not yet been
able to determine
"how such an oafish
man is so attractive
"to these poor young women."
(PRACTICING SOMBER TUNE)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
(KNOCKING CONTINUES)
Really?
Look. if I had anybody
else I could talk to
about this stuff. I'd go there.
I feel like I should complain.
but I'm just not in that
mode right now. Come on.
You know anything
about Ziegevolk?
A little. They're
mostly like preachers.
game-show hosts. you
know? Actor types. you know?
Guys who like to be in the public
eye. Why? Did one goat out on you?
Yeah. Do you know some?
I knew one. In high school.
Elvis Greenspan.
Got all the chicks.
like every hottie
in school. okay?
Kid was 5'4".
weighed in at like 280.
It's hard to believe. but Ziegevolk
give off this. sort of. scent.
You mean like pheromones?
Yeah. They secrete it in
their sweat or something.
Chicks can't resist it.
And if one of these
goat guys touches you.
look out. man. They own you.
Why do you think
those Hollywood types
are always hugging
everybody. right?
Would they ever kill?
No. Bluebeards
have got a bad rap.
They're lovers. not
fighters. you know?
They like to have
a lot of females
hanging off their every word.
Not exactly the
monogamous type. you know?
They live for the rut.
The what? The rut.
Picking out the choicest
females. you know?
For breeding.
You see them in
bars all the time.
They're players. one
night stand type guys.
What are you thinking?
I'm just wondering why certain
people are attracted to each other?
It's all about chemistry.
Oh! Well. that explains
Dale Armistead.
The guy who stole your...
Guy. your first love.
That wasn't love.
Well. it certainly wasn't
looks or intelligence.
You're one to talk. I
met your first girlfriend.
Okay. that was not
chemistry. that was stupidity.
Well. how do you know you're
not being stupid by being with me?
I don't. I just... I think that
there's a lot more to it than that.
You know. in biology. like
systems tend to integrate.
That's so romantic.
How about we get the shopping
done and go home and integrate?
Give me the list and
get the car started.
Lab results on the glass removed
from the gashes on Faith's arm.
It was regular window glass.
So it must have come from
a house or an apartment.
Maybe she was trying
to break out of a window.
Well. we know she was
running from something.
What do you got on Capra?
Well. all I got is that
he moved into town
about a year and a half ago.
bought the bed and breakfast.
I'm having a little trouble on
the background before that.
I think our boy must
have changed his name.
But I did get a hell of
a hit on missing women
here in Portland in
the last six months.
One came from Los Angeles.
another from Seattle.
and a third from Eugene.
All open cases.
Are there other clusters
like this in other cities?
I think we'd better find out.
NICK: It's the same story
with each one of these women.
They all came here in the
last four months and vanished.
Any record of these women
staying at Capra's place?
No. but then we figured he wouldn't
want any record of them staying there.
And we think Faith
got away from him.
then he hunted her
down and killed her.
We also found three other
clusters of missing women.
One in Detroit four years
ago. seven women there.
Another batch in Des
Moines two years ago.
Six women there. And four
women in Tucson in 2000.
HANK: Here's the
really weird thing.
all 17 women were eventually
found alive. 14 of them pregnant.
The DNA checked out to be
the same father for each one.
So we got ourselves a
serial rapist. not a serial killer.
This guy is
definitely a breeder.
Well. can you connect him to
Des Moines. Detroit. Tucson?
We're working on it. We think he
changes his identity every time he moves.
Any of the women
able to identify him?
No. Every testimony
made it sound like
they were kept in
isolated conditions
using some kind of gas
to keep them disoriented.
They didn't know where they
were or who was holding them.
If this is the same guy here in
Portland. we need to be watching him.
Well. you guys keep watch. and
just make sure he doesn't burn you.
We're on it.
Bon appétit.
(AIR HISSING)
(BEEPING SOFTLY)
Piece of cake. We're good to go.
We can track this guy anywhere.
Working.
We're set.
Now all we got to do is wait.
Wake me when something happens.
(DOOR OPENS)
Wake up. Not funny.
No. he's coming out. What?
He's not taking the car?
He's got to take the damn
car. I just got under the car
and got a grease
spot for nothing?
All right. I'm going
to follow him on foot.
You stay here. take a
look around the house.
See if you can find
that broken window.
That'll give us our warrant.
which will give us our DNA.
(ANIMALS CHITTERING)
(BIRD SQUAWKS)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Hello.
Hey. it's Nick.
How did you get
my new cell phone?
Are you kidding me? I'm a cop.
I need your help.
(LAUGHS)
I can pay you. Seriously?
What do I got to do?
All you have to
do is go to a bar...
That I can do.
And watch a guy and
tell me what he does.
Okay. Who's buying the drinks?
Me.
All right. Where
do I have to be?
Blue Moon bar. You know it?
Do I know it? Dude. I'm there.
Shut the door.
You should rethink this.
(IN FRENCH)
First mistake was
coming to my city.
Second mistake was not knowing
who you have to kneel before.
Your fellow reaper brought
this death upon himself.
He followed the Grimm
here. That gives him the right.
He came without my permission.
I claim my revenge
for his death.
Funny. I deny it.
Are you protecting a Grimm?
(SCREAMING)
(IN FRENCH)
(PANTING)
Okay. who am I supposed to be?
Just yourself.
That's a little disappointing.
Okay. there's a
Ziegevolk in the bar.
He's average height.
kind of. on the skinny side.
I know a Ziegevolk
when I smell one. okay?
All right. call me
when you get inside.
I want to know what he
does and who he talks to.
How come you're not doing this?
He's seen me.
He knows I'm a cop.
Plus. I want you to do it
because you know
about Ziegevolk.
Oh! Grimm work.
(LAUGHS)
One more thing.
I saw him eating a toad.
Dude. he's a toad-eater?
That means he's not just a
breeder. he's a herder. okay?
That's actually very
rare for a Ziegevolk.
Well. rare or not. this
guy is a serial rapist.
You got to get inside.
I need to know what he's doing.
(SIGHING) Okay.
Seriously? Come on.
That's like a beer
and half an onion ring.
Half an onion ring.
(INDISTINCT)
Got him.
Well. what's he doing? Trolling.
Talking to a very
attractive woman.
He's got game tonight.
That must have been
one potent toad he ate.
I can smell him from here.
Well. can you get closer to him?
I need to hear what he's saying.
Check this out.
I am moving in on the bar.
Excuse me. pal.
There's an opening
directly to her left.
I'm about 20 feet
from the bar right now.
I can be at the opening...
Okay. I don't need to know
everything you're doing.
Well. excuse me
for being thorough.
Sorry. I'm not talking to you.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Yeah?
HANK: Hey. Nick. I think I
found the window that was broken.
I found a sliver
of glass outside
and the putty around
the window was new.
You're inside the house?
We got probable cause here.
I'm going to see if I can get a sample
of that guy's DNA. You still got him?
Yeah. he's at the Blue Moon bar.
You can see him? Yeah.
Don't let him make you.
No. I'm being careful.
Call me if he starts back here.
Human beings are
malleable. right?
I think everyone needs
emotional and physical rebirth.
I totally agree.
Right? Yeah.
But you got to have some
place to do it. Uh-huh.
Barkeep. double dead
guy. please. Thanks.
A sanctuary. a place
where the world can't intrude.
a retreat for
people just like you.
WOMAN: That sounds
like exactly what I need.
BILLY: Yeah? WOMAN: Yeah.
BILLY: It's simple.
(CHUCKLES)
What a great name.
"Bramble Haus."
Thank you.
Do you know the Bramble bushes.
they extend these long arching
canes that at first don't flower.
but then with a loving touch
produce a succulent fruit
that is just
bursting with flavor.
Double dead.
Wow.
Any time you want to come by.
just call the number
or stop on by.
(WOMAN MOANING)
(MOANING CONTINUES)
(AIR HISSING)
(HISSING)
(GROANING)
Oh. my God.
(MOANS)
What are you doing?
No way.
Dude. I can't be around
that guy. He's way too potent.
I almost bought him a drink.
No. I need you
to go back inside.
I need to know
what he's going to do.
He's hitting on a girl.
She's buying the
full toad. you know?
He gave her his card. What
more do you need to know?
What? What. now you're mad?
He's coming out.
(WHISPERING) You
want me to track him?
No. You're done.
You did good. Thank you.
You can go home now.
I don't want to go home now.
You know if you like
gardens. I happen to...
Piss off. Okay.
One more. Please.
Hank. come on. where
the hell are you. man?
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Pick up the damn phone!
He's on his way home.
OFFICER: Portland Police.
Yeah. it's Detective Burkhardt.
I need a 20 on
Detective Griffin.
Track his cell.
Tracking now.
Yeah. I'll stay on the line.
(AIR HISSING)
(HISSING STOPS)
Still tracking.
All right. call me back
when you find him.
That was fast.
Why wait? I'm ready.
Fantastic. I'll show you a room.
I promise you won't regret it.
I really want to
see your garden.
It's late. But I think I have one
more tour left in me. Come on.
Remember me?
Of course. yes.
You're the detective.
What can I do for you?
I need to talk to her.
Me?
Would you mind stepping outside?
I just need to ask
you a few questions.
Am I in trouble?
What's this all about?
Just come outside. please.
I'm sure it'll be fine.
Why don't you go with him
and I'll be here
when you get back.
Okay. Okay?
I wish you'd just tell
me what this is all about.
You walked into the middle
of a police investigation.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
I need you to leave
the premises. Now!
Yeah?
OFFICER: We've got a
20 on Detective Griffin.
We've identified the
location as the Bramble Haus.
Bed and Breakfast
on Longacre Road.
Thanks.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Hank?
Hank!
(WOMAN MOANS)
Where are you?
HANK: Nick.
What happened?
I don't know. man.
It's some kind of gas.
Look here.
Are they real?
(AIR HISSING)
He's got some kind
of gas coming in here.
Got to get them out of here.
Yeah. but we have to
shut that gas off first.
We'll come back for them.
Oh!
I couldn't stay away.
Lucky me.
You leaving?
Yes. it's such a lovely night.
I thought that I
would take a drive.
I was hoping I could stay.
Well. why don't you come with me
and we can talk about it. okay?
Okay.
(SCREAMS)
Did you see that?
What are you talking
about? Stand back.
No. the gas is going to blow.
We got to find something
to break this door open.
No time. Just us.
Let's do it.
One. two. three!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Again. One. two. three.
(HISSING STOPS)
(INDISTINCT)
You're going to be
all right now. It's over.
House is clean. car is
gone. He's in the wind.
God. I'd hate to lose
this son of a bitch.
No more than I do.
Let it be my birthday.
You didn't get that
grease spot for nothing.
Here you go.
Thanks.
We should really get going soon.
I can't believe I'm doing this.
I've never done
anything like this before.
Am I crazy?
Maybe I'm crazy to take you.
Are we leaving now?
Stop! Police!
Billy!
Police! Out of the way!
Billy Capra. stay where you are!
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
Get down!
(TIRES SCREECHING) (GROANING)
HANK: This is one sick dude.
NICK: We sent his DNA to
Tucson. Des Moines and Detroit
and I'm betting
it's the same guy.
Well. at least
he's off the streets.
and out of the hotel business.
I can't believe any of these
women want to be near this guy.
You know what? I'm
betting it's the toads.
Yeah. right. toads.
(SCOFFS) If only
it was that easy.
Maybe I'll get me some toads.
See how he likes being in
a cage for the rest of his life.
-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.org ] ==-